The Build Settings can be accessed from the File menu
ビルド設定をファイルメニューからアクセスするには
by going to File - Build Settings.
File - Build Settings を開きます。
A build in development is a term used to describe
開発におけるビルドとは、プロジェクトからエクスポートされた
an exported executable form of your project.
実行ファイルを表す用語です。
And given Unity's multiplatform nature
Unity のマルチプラットフォームの性質から、
this varies for each platform.
これはプラットフォームごとに異なります。
For webplayers Unity will export an HTML file
ウェブプレイヤーにおいては Unity はサンプルの埋め込みコード付きの HTML ファイルに
with example embedding code
エクスポートして、
and a .Unity 3D file which contains your game
ゲーム内容を保有する .unity3D ファイルもビルド結果にふくまれ
and will be run by the Unity webplayer plug-in
ブラウザ上で Unity ウェブプレイヤーにより
in your browser.
実行されます。
For standalone Unity will export an executable version of your game
スタンドアローンの場合、 Unity はゲームの実行ファイルを
for PC, Mac and Linux.
PC, Mac および Linux 向けにエクスポートします。
For iOS Unity exports an Xcode project
iOS においては Unity は XCode プロジェクトをエクスポートして
that can be opened in Apple's Xcode SDK
Apple の XCode SDK により開くことが出来ます。
and run on the device for testing
さらにデバイス上でテストしたり、
and submission to the app store.
AppStore へ提出も出来ます。
For Android Unity exports an APK file
Android では、 Unity は APK ファイルをエクスポートして
that can be opened in the Android SDK.
Android SDK で開くことが出来ます。
Flash exports an SWF file
Flash はアセットとともに SWF ファイルを
associated assets,
エクスポートして
and yet again an HTML file with example embedding code.
またもやサンプル埋め込みコードつきの HTML ファイルが含まれます。
Google Native Client exports a Google Chrome browser
Google Native Client は Google Chrome Browser と互換性のある
compatible webplayer game.
ウェブプレイヤー ゲームをエクスポートします。
And for consoles Unity builds directly to your
そしてコンソールについて、 Unity は直接
hardware development kit.
ハードウェア開発キットに直接ビルドします。
The build settings work with Unity's player settings
ビルド設定は Unity の Player Settings と連動して
to define settings for the build that you create.
作成するビルドの設定を
Split in to cross-platform and per-platform
プラットフォーム共通および、プラットフォーム個別に分かれて定義できます。
you can set some basic values at the top and then choose settings below
いくつかの基本的な値は上で設定して、その下で
that are specific for the platform you are developing for.
開発ターゲットとしているプラットフォーム固有の設定を選択できます。
One thing to note as a beginner
初心者として覚えておくべきことのひとつは
is that the resolution in the Resolution and Presentation area
Resolution および Presentation エリアの解像度は
is the setting you can select for the game view.
ゲームビューで選択できる設定です。
For details of other per-platform settings
その他のプラットフォーム固有設定の詳細については
refer to the manual link below.
以下のマニュアルリンクを参照して下さい。 (翻訳:gamesonytablet)